procon.org 2019-06-28

# Privacy Policy and Disclaimer - ProCon.org

Last updated on: 9/25/2015 9:00:13 AM PST

Privacy Policy and Disclaimer  

**Privacy Policy**

  1. ProCon.org is a nonprofit 501(c)(3) organization. Any information we collect through this website is solely for our own use in managing and improving our service.

  2. When readers offer feedback on our sites we will sometimes post their comments online. To preserve confidentiality, only the writer's first name is usually noted, unless they specifically ask us not to include their first name, or authorize us to use their full name. Respondents are generally notified when we add their response to the Reader Comments sections.

  3. Private information about our users, including names, email addresses, contact information, donation amounts, and other personal data are NOT marketed or sold to any outside party or parties, including the government. Unless we are subpoenaed to do otherwise, our customer's private information shall remain private.

  4. ProCon.org sometimes has links to other sites. Their privacy policies may differ from ours, and we, therefore, can take no responsibility for them.

  5. We collect data about traffic on our sites, including, but not limited, to the number and type of pages viewed. This information is used to improve our sites and aggregate totals some of which are posted on our sites.

  6.   7. We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

  8. ProCon.org uses SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption for improved security when visitors transmit payment information for online donations.

  9. We restrict access to personal information to ProCon.org employees and advisors who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services.

  10. If we decide to change this privacy policy, those changes will be reflected in this Privacy Statement (last updated Nov. 12, 2013).

  11. We welcome your suggestions or comments about our Privacy Policy. Please send your comments to our Managing Editor. 

  12. On May 25, 2018 the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) came into force in all European Union member states. Details about those regulations are here https://gdpr-info.eu/. EU residents who subscribe to the ProCon.org email newsletter have provided their email addresses which can be considered personally identifiable information. ProCon.org uses those email addresses to send opt-in subscribers research updates as they have requested. We do not make other use of the email data. ProCon.org respects user personal data and takes great care to maintain its confidentiality. Recipients can unsubscribe from email newsletters at any time. EU resident donor data are similarly protected with strict confidentiality protocols. 

**Disclaimer**

ProCon.org content is offered as a public benefit in accordance with our 501(c)(3) status. All the information on our sites can be viewed free of charge, and reprinting is allowed under the guidelines outlined in our [Terms of Use](https://www.procon.org/terms-of-use.php) policy. 

The information on the ProCon.org websites has been compiled using the data available to us. We strive for accuracy but cannot be held responsible for any factual errors or mistakenly attributed quotations. We are human and sometimes make mistakes. We make every effort to correct any such errors promptly when they are brought to our attention. Please Contact Us to report any errors on our sites. 

Just because we quote someone does not mean we in any way agree with them or support their perspective. ProCon.org's inclusion of links or references to outside sites or organizations is not intended to in any way endorse the views expressed or products/services offered by those third parties. Similarly, we bear no responsibility for the content or views expressed on sites that link to a ProCon.org website.
